<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Awards | Proochista Ariana</title>
    <link>/awards/</link>
      <atom:link href="/awards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Awards</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-gb</language><copyright>&amp;copy Proochista Ariana 2020</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_huac02e177c48dd037bd1a472866f1ac88_223884_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Awards</title>
      <link>/awards/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Major Educator - Medical Sciences Division - 2019</title>
      <link>/awards/major-educator-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/awards/major-educator-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr Proochista Ariana&lt;/strong&gt; - for the exceptional impact her vision, integrity, commitment and skills have made towards the success of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ndm.ox.ac.uk/msc-international-health-and-tropical-medicine&#34;&gt;MSc in International Health and Tropical Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, for her capacity building work including through her support for alumni, and for her enthusiasm in encouraging cross-disciplinary collaboration in education.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“A teacher who inspires becomes a role model; and it&#39;s with great confidence that I consider her one. She has truly shown how much she cares about us as individuals and about the great futures she inspires us to seek. It&#39;s because of leaders like her that this course is truly unique.”&lt;/em&gt; [Student]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outstanding Supervisor Award - Medical Sciences - 2017</title>
      <link>/awards/outstanding-supervisor-award-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/awards/outstanding-supervisor-award-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The experience as a graduate student in Oxford is determined by a huge number of things., however having a supportive supervisor can be key. To win this award, the supervisor should:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be willing to spend time and effort working with the supervisee&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Give helpful, prompt, fluent and thoughtful comments&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be a resource in terms of general knowledge about the discipline, research methods and current developments&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Critically engage with their own and their students’ subject matter, both in personal discussions and the wider scientific community&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create a stimulating and consistently challenging research environment, encouraging the student to consider new or alternative perspectives and to push boundaries&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be supportive of students’ professional development, by encouraging and supporting conference participation, teaching, submission of papers, and other relevant activities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be responsive to student concerns and difficulties and aid the supervisee in overcoming challenges themselves&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Develop the supervisee’s independence while always remaining approachable when necessary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Critically engage with their own and their students’ subject matter, both in personal discussions and the wider academic community&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enable the student to progress and build their own network by providing initial contact with others within/outside the research group and pointers to relevant conferences/seminars&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special Recognition Award - 2017</title>
      <link>/awards/special-recognition-award-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/awards/special-recognition-award-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We award the Special Recognition Award to someone who has made a significant and distinctive contribution to an area of University life:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In research&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;College life&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In their Department/Faculty&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To the lives of students&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Acclaimed Lecturer - Medical Sciences Division - 2016</title>
      <link>/awards/most-acclaimed-lecturer-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/awards/most-acclaimed-lecturer-2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lecturers have the unenviable task of leading a group of students through often complicated material at a pace that is engaging to everyone yet leaves no one behind. This award recognises those that do this particularly well, and who make that 9am lecture that much more palatable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For an ideal nominee:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lectures are engaging and informative, leaving the student with a strong grasp of their subject area and a desire to learn more&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lectures are well prepared and supporting information is provided&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lectures are coherently and clearly executed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lecturers express visible enthusiasm for the lecture subject&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lecturers are available to answer questions, approachable, and responsive&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excellent Teacher Award - Medical Sciences Division - 2013</title>
      <link>/awards/excellent-teacher-award-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/awards/excellent-teacher-award-2013/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr Proochista Ariana (Nuffield Department of Population Health) - for work spannning two academic Divisions: she designed and developed the Health &amp;amp; Development module for students of both the MSc in Global Health Science (Medical Sciences) and the MPhil in International Development (Social Sciences). Dr Ariana is widely regarded by students in both disciplines as a &amp;lsquo;facilitator&amp;rsquo; of learning; she is an exemplary proponent of inter-disciplinary teaching.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Acclaimed Lecturer - Medical Sciences Division - 2013</title>
      <link>/awards/most-acclaimed-lecturer-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/awards/most-acclaimed-lecturer-2013/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
